Guide to the Department of Pathology, School of Medicine, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Pathology, School of Medicine, Yale University, records
1936-1981
RU 563
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
50
(40 boxes)
T he records consist of student files, correspondence, research and grant materials, reprints, and reports of department chairman Harry S. N. Greene and grants and contracts of the Department of Pathology at the Yale School of Medicine.
Yale University. School of Medicine
Green, Harry S. N.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 27-E (YRG 27-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Medicine.
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Scope and Contents
T he records consist of student files, correspondence, research and grant materials, reprints, and reports of department chairman Harry S. N. Greene and grants and contracts of the Department of Pathology at the Yale School of Medicine.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Pathology -- Study and teaching; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Departments; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Department of Pathology; Yale University. School of Medicine
- Records, 1936-1968; Accession 1975-A-008
  Conditions Governing Access
  Student files located in box 7 are restricted until Jan 1, 2036 due to University policy set forth by the Yale Corporation.
  - Correspondence files A-R, 1936-53 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence file S-Z, 1936-53 (Box 2)
  - Press clippings, 1954-57 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence A-L, 1954-57 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence M-T, 1958-67 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence A-L, 1958-67 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence M-Z (Box 6)
  - Manuscript correspondence with publishers (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous files (Box 7)
  - Student files, 1958-60 (Box 7)
    These materials are restricted until Jan 1, 2036 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
  - Projects and memorials (Box 7)
  - First drafts and papers (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous and reports re: research (Box 8)
  - Research files (Box 9)
  - Reprints, 1932-1968 (Box 10)
- Records, 1974-1981; Accession 1982-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2017.